Guide to the Julie Braun-Vogelstein Collection, 1743-1971 AR 25034 / MF 473
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series I: Heinrich and Lily Braun, undated, 1800s-1900s
  - (9/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun Correspondence to H.Braun, 1897-1901 (n.r.) (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - (9/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun Correspondence to H.Braun, 1901-1902 (n.r) (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - (9/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun Correspondence to H.Braun, 1903-1904 (n.r.) (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - (10/1) Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun: correspondence Lilly Braun to Heinrich Braun, 1905-6 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - (10/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun: correspondence Lilly Braun to Heinrich Braun, 1907-1908 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - (10/3): Julie Braun Vogelstein and Lilly Braun: correspondence Lilly Braun to Heinrich Braun, 1909-1910 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - (10/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun: correspondence Lilly Braun to Heinrich Braun, 1911-1912 (n.r. !) (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - (10/6): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun: correspondence Lilly Braun to Heinrich Braun, 1916; Telegrams, 1896-1914 (n.r. !) (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - (11/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1895-96 (n.r.!) (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - (10/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Lilly Braun: correspondence Lilly Braun to Heinrich Braun, 1913-1914 (n.r. !) (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - (11/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1896; 1898-1899 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - (11/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1900-1901 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - (11/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1902-1903 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - (11/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1904-1905 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence, inventory, Box 11 files 3- 5 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - (12/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and HeinrichBraun: correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1906-1907 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - (12/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1908-1909 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - (12/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1910-1911 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - (12/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence to Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1912-1913 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - (12/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun: correspondence Heinrich Braun to Lilly Braun, 1914-1916 (n.r.) (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - (13/1): Heinrich Braun to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1913-1917 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - (13/2): Heinrich Braun to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1918-1919 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - (13/3): Heinrich Braun to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - (13/4): Heinrich Braun to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1921-1923 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - (13/5): Heinrich Braun to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - (13/6): Heinrich Braun to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1925-1927 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - (14/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - (14/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - (14/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1915-1916 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - (14/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - (14/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - (14/6): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - (15/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - (15/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - (15/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - (15/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - (16/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - (16/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - (16/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Heinrich Braun, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - (17/1): Letters to Heinrich Braun and Julie Braun-Vogelstein on Heinrich's book, 1918-1924 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - (17/2): Letters to Heinrich Braun and Julie Braun-Vogelstein on Heinrich's book, 1919-1925 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - (17/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Lily Braun, 1914-1916 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - (17/4): Ludwig Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun, 1915-1927 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - (17/5): Rosa Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun, 1912-1919 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - (17/6): Rudolf Borchardt and Heinrich Braun and J.B-Vogelstein, 1905-1927 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - (18/1): Professor Hildebrandt to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1920-1931 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - (18/2): Professor Hildebrandt to Julie Braun-Vogelstein, 1932-1939 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - (18/3): Miscellaneous A-W, correspondence, 1906-1943 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - (18/4): Heinrich Braun: Herr Heymann, Heuss- Knapp, JastrowJulie Braun-Vogelstein Kautzky, A.Braun, 1901-1931 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - (18/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein and Heinrich Braun, correspondence, Auerbach, Hallgarten, 1896-1908; Huymans-Adler, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - (18/6): Heinrich Braun correspondence Hartmann, Hermann Schultze-Gaevernitz, Eckerl, 1894-1924 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 1-101, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - (19): ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 102-205, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, manuscript, page 206-324, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 1-84, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 1-111, Chapter X-XI, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 1-184, Chapter XII, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 1-175, Chapter XIII, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 1-155, Chapter XIV, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - (19): Ein Menschen Leben Biography of H.Braun, Manuscript, page 1-157, Chapter XV, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 153)
- Series II: Otto Braun, undated, 1800s-1900s
  - (1/1): Otto Braun: Schoolpapers, 1904-1918 (N.R.) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - (1/2): Otto Braun: Essays and other writings by Otto Braun as a child, 1907-1912 (N.R.) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - (1/3): Otto Braun: Zeitschrift Der Anfang, 1908-1910 (N.R.) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - (1/4): Otto Braun: Biographical information by Lily Braun and Professor Petzold., 1907- 10 (N.R.) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - (1/5): Military Documents (mainly about Otto's death), Sterbeurkunde and Photos, 1916-1918 (N.R.) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - (2/1): Poetry, Manuscripts, 1909-1913 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - (2/2): Essays, 1909-1913 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - (2/3): Wesen des Staates I, (no date) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - (2/4): Wesen des Staates II, (no date) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - (2/5): Otto Braun Poems, 1909-1917 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - (2/6): Otto Braun Poems, Plays, 1906-1917 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - (3/1): Otto Braun Correspondence, 1905-1908 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - (3/2): Otto Braun, Correspondence, 1909-1913 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - (3/3): Lily Braun to Otto Braun, 1904-1908 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - (3/4): Lily Braun to Otto Braun, 1911-1914 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - (3/5): Correspondence: w/ Otto Braun letters set aside for Otto Buch, 1907-1911 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - (3/6): Otto Braun Note Book Excerpts, 1906-1910 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diary, volume 1., 1904-1906 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries, volumes 2-3., 1908-1909 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries volumes 4-5., 1909 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries volumes 6-7., 1910 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries volumes 8-9, w. insert, 1910 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries volumes 10-11, 1910-1911 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries volumes 12-13, w/inserts, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries volumes 14-15, 1911-1912 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diaries volumes 16-17, 1912-1913 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diary volume 18, 1913-1914 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - (4): Otto Braun Diary volume 19, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - (4): Otto Braun War Diaries volumes 1-2., 1914-1915 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - (4): Otto Braun War Diaries volumes 3-4., 1915-1917 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - (4): Otto Braun War Diaries volumes 5-6, 1917-1918 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - (4): Otto Braun War Diary Volume 7., 1918 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - (4): Otto Braun Last Thoughts Book., 1913-[1921] (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - (5/1): Otto Braun Correspondence, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - (5/2): Otto Braun Correspondence, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - (5/3): Otto Braun Correspondence, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - (5/4): Otto Braun and Heinrich Braun Correspondence, 1917 (N.R) (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - (6/1): Otto Braun and Heinrich Braun Correspondence, 1905-1918 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - (6/2): Otto Braun and Lily Braun. Correspondence, 1915-1916 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - (6/3): Otto Braun and Julie Braun-V. Correspondence, 1914-1918 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - (6/4): Otto Braun and Heinrich Braun Correspondence, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - (7/1): Otto Braun: Correspondence., 1909-1918 (n.r.) (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - (7/2): Otto Braun and Julie Braun V. Correspondence inc. Drawings, 1914-1918 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - (7/3): Otto Braun and Otto Gruender. Correspondence, 1909-1917 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - (7/4): Karin, Braun and F, Paesler, Petzold, Correspondence, 1910-1918 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - (7/5): Lepuis, Neusser, Correspondence, 1910-1917 (n.r.) (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - (7/6): Otto Braun and Lily Braun to Hans Braun Correspondence, 1905-1917 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - (8/1): Otto Braun Condolences, Correspondence, 1918 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - (8/2): Otto BraunMilitary notes,also H. Braun Correspondence, 1915-1918 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - (8/3): Otto Braun 10th Anniversary of Death, Clippings, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - (8/4): Otto Braun Julie Braun Vogelstein re. Assorted.Manuscripts, c.1911-1928 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - (8/5): Otto Braun, Manuscripts, Lectures and Correspondence re., 1899; 1930; 1951-57. (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - (8/6): Otto Braun, Ein Versuch....Welt Anschauung, ( n.d.) (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - (8/7): Otto Braun, Translations, ( n.d.) (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - (8/8): Otto Braun, A.Braun, Gehub, Porthea von Kunkel, Correspondence, 1908-1918 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - (9/1): Otto Braun, Reviews of Otto Braun's Writings Fragments Clippings, 1919-1923 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - (9/2): Otto Braun, Critical Reviews of Otto Braun book, Fragments, Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - (9/3): Otto Braun Book Manuscript, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - (9/4): Otto Braun-Vogelstein: to Julie Braun-V.re. Otto Braun book, Correspondence, 1957,1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - (9/5): Otto Braun Otto Braun book material, Correspondence, Clippings, Periodicals, etc., 1919-1924 (n.r.) (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - (10/1): Otto Braun Correspondence re.Otto's Book, 1918-1927 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - (10/2): Correspondence to JB-V and H.B. about Otto's Book, 1915-1926 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - (10/3): Otto Braun Reviews of Otto Braun book, 1921-1924 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - (10/4): Otto Braun Reviews of Otto Braun book, 1920-1929 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - (10/5): Otto Braun Clippings, 1924; 1932-35 (n.r.) (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - (10/6): English Notes to Otto Braun, 1923 (n.r.) (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - (10/7): Otto Braun English and Italian articles re. Otto Braun book, 1922-1924 (n.r.) (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - (10/8): Otto Braun, Breslauer Nachrichten Newspaper clipping, re. Otto Braun Writings, June 26., 1927 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - (10/9): Lily Braun, Genealogy Family tree., n.d. (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - (11): Otto Braun, Lily Braun Diary of Infancy w/photos., 1897-1904 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - (11): Otto Braun Autograph book, 1906-1917 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - (11): Otto Braun J.BV Account Book re. Otto B. book, 1920-1923 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - (11): Otto Braun Periodicals w/Articles on Otto Braun, 1915-1920 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - (11): Otto Braun, Periodicals w/Articles on OB, 1921-1926 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - (11): Otto Braun, Book Prospectus, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - (11): Otto Braun Pictures as Officer, Candidate, Carte de Visite. (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Series III: Ludwig Vogelstein, undated, 1800s-1900s
  - (1/1): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1911 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - (1/2): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1912 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - (1/3): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1913 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - (1/4): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1913 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - (1/5): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1914 [n.r.]. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - (1/6): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1915 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - (1/7): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1916-1917 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - (2/1): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - (2/2): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - (2/3): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1923 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - (2/4): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - (3/1): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - (3/2): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - (3/3): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - (3/4): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - (3/5): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - (3/6): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 [n.r] (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - (3/7): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - (3/8): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925. [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - (3/9): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1926 [n.r] (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - (3/10): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1926 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - (3/11): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1926 [n.r.] (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - (4/1): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - (4/2): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1927 n.r (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - (4/3): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - (4/4): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - (4/5): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1928 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - (4/6): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1928 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - (4/7): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1928 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - (4/8): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1929 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - (4/9): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1929 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - (4/10): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1929 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - (5/1): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - (5/2): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - (5/3): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - (5/4): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1930 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - (5/5): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1931 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - (6/1): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1932 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - (6/2): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1932 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - (6/3): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, 1932 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - (6/4): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, 1932 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - (6/5): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1933 n.r (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - (6/6): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1933 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - (6/7): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1932 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - (6/8): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1932 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - (6/9): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1932 n.r. (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - (6/10): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1932-1934 n.r.. (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - (7/1): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1933 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - (7/2): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1933 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - (7/3): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1934 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - (7/4): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1934 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - (7/5): Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1899-1931 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - (7/6): Ludwig Vogelstein Passports, 1903-30 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - (7/7): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, Condolences, 1934 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - (8/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1889; 1893; 1906-1908, N.R. (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - (8/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1908-1909 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - (8/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1910 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - (8/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1911 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - (8/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - (9/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - (9/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence PostCards, 1913 n.r. (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - (9/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1914. (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - (9/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1915 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - (9/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1916 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - (9/6): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1917-1918 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - (9/7): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - (10/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1920 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - (10/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1920 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - (10/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1921 N.R. (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - (10/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - (10/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - (10/6): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - (11/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - (11/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1922 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - (11/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - (11/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - (11/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - (11/6): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - (12/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - (12/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - (12/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - (12/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - (12/5): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - (13/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - (13/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - (13/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - (13/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - (14/1): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - (14/2): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - (14/3): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - (14/4): Julie Braun-Vogelstein to Ludwig Vogelstein correspondence, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - (15/1): Postcards of Ludwig Vogelstein to his parents, 1888-1912 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - (15/2): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his parents, 1899-1897 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - (15/3): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his parents, 1898-1904 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - (15/4): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his parents, 1900; 1912; 1916; 1919. (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - (15/5): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his parents, 1907-1914 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - (15/6): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his mother Rosa also letters by Theodor, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - (15/7): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his mother, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - (15/8): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his mother, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - (15/9): Letters of Ludwig Vogelstein to his mother, 1915-1920 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - (16/1): Ludwig Vogelstein: Biographical Material and Correspondence, 1931-1960. (Box 17, Folder 101)
  - (16/2): Ludwig Vogelstein:Condolence Correspondence on his death, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 102)
  - (16/3): Ludwig Vogelstein:Obituaries, Newspaper Clippings Oct., Nov., 1934 (Box 17, Folder 103)
  - (16): Ludwig Vogelstein: Mendriam Testimonial, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 104)
  - (16): Ludwig Vogelstein: Death Testimonial US Metals Refining Company, 18 Dec.1934. (Box 17, Folder 105)
  - (16): Ludwig Vogelstein: Death Testimonial American Metal Compnay, Ltd., 27. Sept. 1934. (Box 17, Folder 106)
  - (16): Ludwig Vogelstein: Death Testimonial Central Savings Bank, NY., 8 Oct. 1934. (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - (16): Ludwig Vogelstein:Memorial Album, 1934. (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - (17/1): Ludwig Vogelstein:Correspondence Birthday, 1918,1931. (Box 17, Folder 109)
  - (17/2): Ludwig Vogelstein:Correspondence re: Hirsch and Sohn, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - (17/3): Ludwig Vogelstein: and Theodore (father), 1904-1929. (Box 17, Folder 111)
  - (17/4): Ludwig Vogelstein: Correspondence re. J. Dreyfus and Co., Berlin Ludwg, Theodore Julie, 1930-1932 (Box 17, Folder 112)
  - (17/5): Ludwig Vogelstein: Personal Correspondence Hirsch and Ludwig Vogelstein, 1903,1907-1914; 1933 (Box 17, Folder 113)
  - Ludwig Vogelstein: Temple Beth-El, Golden Jubilee, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - (17/6): Ludwig Vogelstein:Photos, Old New York, c.1901-1910 (Box 17, Folder 115)
  - (17/7): Ludwig Vogelstein: Documents, Correspondence re: American Metal Co., 1919-1958 (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - (17/8): Ludwig Vogelstein: Documents, Alien Property Custodian. Documents related to surrender of stock., 1918-1919 (Box 17, Folder 117)
  - (17/9): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, H v. R. Vogelstein Foundation, 1923-1926 (Box 17, Folder 118)
  - (17/10): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, Misc., 1923-1933 (Box 17, Folder 119)
  - (17/11): Ludwig Vogelstein, Correspondence,Business Letters to L.V. 1931, Carl Loeb, President, Otto Sussman, VP, American Metal Company, Annual Report 1925; Letter from Carl Loeb to Ludwig, 1923., 1923-1931 (Box 17, Folder 120)
  - (17/12): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence of LV and various memebers from Aron Hirsch, 1896-1933 (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - (17/13): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence,Business, Aron Hirsch, 1896-1933 (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - (18/2): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence w. Family and G. Goldschmidt, 1890-1907 (Box 17, Folder 123)
  - (18/3): Ludwig Vogelstein Correspondence, Letters between Ludwig and Gutentags (cousins), 1989-1929 (Box 17, Folder 124)